<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Portfolio</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Aakash Chauhan</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">aakashch.code@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="name">Aakash Chauhan</string>
    <string name="role">Android Developer</string>
    <string name="description">
I’m Aakash Harishchandra Chauhan, a passionate Android developer and tech enthusiast, currently in my second year of BE in Electronics &amp; Telecommunication Engineering (EXTC). Even though my branch is not primarily focused on programming, I’ve always been fascinated by coding and love turning ideas into real world applications.

My main interest lies in Android development, where I specialize in backend integration, API handling (including Gemini API and other third party REST APIs using Retrofit), and cloud storage with Firebase — skills I am continuing to strengthen with hands on practice.

One of my proudest projects is Intelli Wealth, a production level finance manager app that boosted my confidence and taught me how to build scalable, user friendly solutions. I’ve also explored MERN development, but I discovered my true passion lies in Android development and creating smooth, interactive mobile experiences.

Recently, I’ve been expanding into AI powered applications. I completed the Oracle Race to Certification program in Generative AI and gained practical experience with Oracle Cloud Infrastructure (OCI). Exploring the intersection of mobile apps and AI excites me the most, and I’m always curious to learn, experiment, and improve with every project.

For me, coding is not just about writing programs it’s about solving problems, learning continuously, and building technology that makes a difference.
</string>
    <string name="project_number">4+</string>
    <string name="projects">Projects</string>
    <string name="Experience">Fresher</string>
    <string name="tech_numbers">25+</string>
    <string name="technologies_number">Technologies</string>
    <string name="java">Java</string>
    <string name="mvvm">MVVM</string>
    <string name="room_database">Room Database</string>
    <string name="get_in_touch">Get In Touch</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="linkedin">LinkedIn</string>
    <string name="github">GitHub</string>
    <string name="skills_amp_technologies"><![CDATA[Skills & Technologies]]></string>
    <string name="featured_projects">Featured Projects</string>
    <string name="view_all">View All</string>
    <string name="mpandroidchart">MPAndroidChart</string>
    <string name="achievements">Achievements</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="mail">aakashch.code@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="location">Mumbai, India</string>
</resources>